<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on LABHDUFRJ</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on LABHDUFRJ</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bruno José Rodrigues Durães</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/1_brunoduraes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/1_brunoduraes/</guid>
      <description>Sociologist, professor of Sociology at UFRJ (Department of Sociology/IFCS); Former professor at the Federal University of Recôncavo da Bahia (UFRB) and UNIFAL-MG; Holds a PhD in Social Sciences (Unicamp-2011), a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Sociology (Unicamp-2006), and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Sociology (UFBA-2004); Specializes in Sociology of Work, focusing on themes such as digital labor, informality, Marxist theory, and sociology education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexandre Barbosa Fraga</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/2_alexandrebarbosa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/2_alexandrebarbosa/</guid>
      <description>Adjunct Professor at the Department of Sociology at the Institute of Social Sciences of UERJ; Holds a PhD in Sociology from PPGSA/UFRJ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joyce Louback</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/3_joycelouback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/3_joycelouback/</guid>
      <description>Sociologist and professor at the Faculty of Education at the Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (UFRJ), in the Department of Education Foundations; Holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s and PhD in Sociology from the Institute of Social and Political Studies (IESP-UERJ); Focuses on themes related to Brazil&amp;rsquo;s redemocratization, collective action, peripheral associativism, and sociology of education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>José Victor Yunes da Cunha</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/4_josevictor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/4_josevictor/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences - UFRJ, with applied knowledge in Python programming, data exploratory analysis in R, and statistics (studies conducted at UFRJ&amp;rsquo;s Actuarial Science); Currently focused on research on Inequality and Big Data, with a strong interest in integrating qualitative and quantitative methodologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabriely Silva Fraga</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/5_gabrielysilva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/5_gabrielysilva/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences at the Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (UFRJ); Volunteer researcher at UFRJ&amp;rsquo;s Digital Humanities Laboratory (LABHDUFRJ); Also works as a volunteer in the Campo-Cidade Project, developing management and strengthening tools for the MST&amp;rsquo;s Armazém do Campo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sabrina Lima</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/6_sabrinalima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/6_sabrinalima/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences at UFRJ and a volunteer researcher at UFRJ&amp;rsquo;s Digital Humanities Laboratory (LABHDUFRJ); She has taken several complementary courses in sociology and digital humanities, focusing on understanding the reinvention of humanities in the face of technological evolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renan Aguiar do Nascimento</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/7_renanaguiar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/7_renanaguiar/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences Teaching at UFRJ, with a focus on the sociology of work, political sociology, and education; Conducted studies on digital informal labor and influencers as new forms of informal work, as well as research on the National Liberation Action during Brazil&amp;rsquo;s military dictatorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maria Lúcia Cordeiro</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/8_marialucia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/8_marialucia/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences Teaching at UFRJ and a certified Occupational Safety Technician from CEFET-RJ; Participates in UFRJ&amp;rsquo;s Digital Humanities Laboratory and the &amp;lsquo;Sociology in Play&amp;rsquo; extension project; Develops research on the New High School implementation and urban sociabilities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
